刚出炉热气腾腾的小蛋糕
Fresh warm cupcakes!
来杯热可可 好好享受这冬日仙境吧
Enjoy this winter wonderland with some hot, hot cocoa!
我们早该打烊 躺在地板上打盹了
Why are we open and selling to no one
为什么还坚持开门营业 卖蛋糕给暴风雪吗
when we should be closed and taking a floor nap?
没错 麦克斯 现在是暴风雪
Yes, Max, it's a blizzard right now,
但一个小时内 温度将会升到摄氏18度
but in an hour, it could be 65!
这就是全球变暖的好处
That's the beauty of global warming.
你给我站住
You, stop!
我送你一根薄荷彩棒哦
I'll give you a peppermint stick!
那只是一根红色条纹吸管而已
That is a straw with red stripes.
那哪个听起来比较好 麦克斯
Well, what sounds better, Max,
薄荷彩棒还是
a peppermint stick or...
"红色条纹吸管"
"a straw with red stripes"?
首先我要说 你学我还真像
First of all, great impression of me.
其次 现在这种鬼天气
And second, no one in their right mind
没有一个正常人会停下来买蛋糕的
is stopping for cupcakes right now.
姑娘们
Oh, hi, girls!
猜谁想来个小蛋糕
Guess who wants a cupcake.
是我哦
It's me.
给 苏菲
Here you go, Sophie.
麦克斯 瞧 我们有顾客了
See, Max, we have a customer.
对了如你所知 我不会付钱的哦
And just so you know, I'm not gonna pay.
真开心你们还在营业
I am so glad you stay open
雪花满天飞还坚持不懈
even with all this snow everywhere.
你们俩干得很好
You know, good for you.
真的把心血都倾注到这小蛋糕窗口上了
You two are really committed to this little cupcake window,
即使明知没人买 也还坚持营业
Even when it's stupid.
够了 咱们收工吧
That's it, we're closing.
这街道该铲雪[开搞]的程度
These streets need to be plowed
比那个老婆肚子大了的明星还严重
more than that poor married Jonas brother.
先等等 你听
No, wait. Listen!
是铲雪车的声音
It's the snowplow.
铲完雪 顾客上门就轻松了
Now, people will be able to get to us.
跟你说了今晚也会是个
I told you, it is gonna be one of those
纽约城神奇魔法之夜
magical New York city nights.
老天麻烦再爱她一遍
Do it again!
我们还待在这干嘛
Why are we here?
外面还在下雪 店里一个客人都没有
It's still snowing, and we have no customers.
我都得靠自己塞钱进收银机里
I had to put money in the cash register
才能满足偷钱欲了
just to steal it.
我们不能说走就走 阿憨还没来啊
We can't just leave. Han's not here.
可能火车停止发车
Maybe the trains aren't running,
或者小阿憨被一片雪花给击晕了
or Han got knocked out by a snowflake.
餐厅的规矩我想你懂 就我现编出来的这条
Well, you know the diner rule, the one I just made up.
如果他迟到超过30分钟
If he's 30 minutes late,
我们就偷走所有能塞进口袋里的东西开溜
we grab whatever we can fit in our pockets and leave.
行啊 如果他迟到了31分钟
Of course, if he's 31 minutes late
发现店里没人在 大家就全被炒了
and there's no one here, we all get fired.
但要我说就碰运气吧
But I say we roll the dice.
先不管他发生了啥事
Well, whatever happened,
但他不在我们就没法营业啊
we can't run the diner if Han's not here.
有见地 那我们谁要负责在店里转悠
That's right, who's gonna walk around here
然后想着阴道到底长哪样
guessing what a vagina looks like?
我咩
Uh, me?
上菜
Pick up.
我喜欢这种冷天气
I like this cold weather.
我可以戴上我的金豹帽
I get to wear my chin-cheetah hat.
金豹 世上哪有这种动物啊
Chin-cheetah? That's not even a real animal.
真的有 我这帽子就是用最后一只做的
Yes, it is. This was the last one.
那食物要给谁 店里都没客人
Who's that food for? We don't have any customers.
是我跟迪克要吃
It's for me and Deke.
我们要在小蛋糕店里读烘焙学校的东西
We're studying pastry school stuff in the cupcake shop.
也要在雪球里包石头用来丢那些
We're also putting rocks in snowballs and throwing them
戴着白痴填充动物帽的嬉皮士
at hipsters wearing those stupid stuffed animal hats.
麦克斯 你觉得明天还用去学校吗
Max, you think school will be open?
我还希望能休息一天
I was hoping it'd be closed,
让我有一天时间清静
so I'd have at least have one day
不用再烦心我跟尼可拉斯大厨之间
where I wouldn't have to deal with the drama
烦人的情事
between me and chef Nicolas.
就是你亲了的那个已婚男人吗
Oh, is that the married man you kissed?
谁跟你说这事的
Who told you?
你啊 说了几百次
You! Like a hundred times.
来玩个下雪天游戏吧
Let's play a snow day game.
比如 来猜阿憨办公室里保险箱的密码吗
Like what, guess the code to the safe in Han's office?
我知道头两个数字是8与9
I know the first two numbers are eight and nine.
如果得在我们这群人中
How about-- if you could have sex
选一个人做爱 你们会选谁
with anyone here, who would it be?
是"想要与之"还是"被迫与之"
"Could have" or "forced to have"?
奥列格 你先来吧
Oleg, you go first.
我选卡洛琳
I pick Caroline.
谢谢 真是恶心爆了
Oh, thank you. That's gross.
不能选她 她在雪中被熊一掌拍死了
No, Caroline got mauled by a bear in the snow.
真的吗
I did?
不是 是我穿着熊衣服干的
No, it was me in a bear costume.
我下手时她完全没料到
She never saw me coming.
所以我只能在你跟厄尔之间选吗
So my only two choices are you or Earl?
不 厄尔在睡梦中去世了
No, Earl passed away in his sleep.
是是是 等过几周
Of course, you'll feel terrible
你一语成谶了 我看你笑不笑得出来
when that happens in a couple of weeks.
抱歉失陪了 我要回家
Now, if you'd excuse me, I'm going to go home
好好爽一发了
and roll me a fatty.
她的名字叫蒂妮湿
Her name is Denise.
好吧 那我选你
Okay, so I pick you.
我吗
Me?
你从两个人选中选了我吗
You pick me out of all these two people?
路易斯 你脸红啦
Luis, are you blushing?
我只是有擦腮红而已
No! I'm wearing blush.
大家不用担心了
Don't worry, everyone!
我没死
I survived!
还是不知道阿憨上哪了
Still don't know where Han is,
但新的007电影坏人登场了
but the new Bond villain just arrived.
比"八爪女"更厉害的八"逼"女来了
Now there's an even bigger octopussy in town.
迟到真是太对不起了
I'm very sorry I'm late.
我被困在雪堆里了
I got stuck in a snow bank,
靠撒尿才融出一条逃生道
and I had to pee myself out.
麦克斯呢 我知道她肯定不是被困雪中
Where's Max? And I know she's not trapped in the storm,
因为她就是教我
'cause she's the one who taught me
尿出一条雪路的人
how to pee my way out.
麦克斯 这看起来像一堆闪亮蛋蛋的
Max, what is the French name for this pastry
法国糕点叫做什么名字呢
that looks like a bunch of glazed balls?
叫瞎瞎瞎吗
A sha-sha-sha?
不是
No.
叫呼噜呼噜呼噜吗
A doh-doh-doh-doh-doh?
很接近了 是"啪嗒秋"
Oh, so close. It's a "Pata-chow."
烘焙学校还得读法语跟化学
French and chemistry for pastry school?
我本来以为上课只会是
I thought class was gonna be like,
"哪个比较好 蛋糕还是面包
"which is better, cake or bread?
当然是两种都好啦
They're both great, duh.
很好 学位证拿去吧"
Here's your degree."
我有个坏消息
I have terrible news.
阿憨没死 还要我们帮忙干别的活
Han's not dead, and he wants us to do side work.
能别打扰吗
Do you mind?
我跟哈利·大麻特在学习呢
Harry Pothead and I are trying to study.
麦克斯 我知道怎么过关了
Oh, Max, I know how we'll pass.
我们可以请教我们学校隔壁桌的那个女生
We can ask that girl next to us in class for help.
她会说法语
She speaks French.
就是那个屁股大如球的女人 朱迪
You know, the one with the bubble butt, Judy?
知道 大屁股朱迪嘛
Oh, yeah! Judy with the booty.
你跟人家没熟到可以叫小名
You don't know her that well.
请称呼人家全名"大屁股小姐朱迪丝"
Please, call her "Judith with the boodith."
麦克斯 我能打断你们这集"屁股有约"吗
Max, can I interrupt this episode of "Ass chat"
然后跟你到外面谈两句吗
and talk to you outside for a second?
-行 -麦克斯
- Sure. - Hey, Max.
她屁股大到得用狗爬式才能进屋
Her butt's so big, she walks into the room doggie-style.
我要说的话 就跟我叔叔半夜走近我房间时
Like I said to my uncle when he came into my bedroom
我说的话一样 "最好是够爽"
in the middle of the night, "this better be good."
迪克跟你像好兄弟之间
Does it bother you when Deke talks
聊别的妞的时候你不会不爽吗
about other girls with you like you're a guy?
你把我当闺蜜一样
Not as much as it bothers me
谈天说地时 我更不爽呢
when you talk to me like I'm a girl.
迪克跟我只是兄弟
Look, Deke and I are just bros.
我对他又没"性趣"
I don't want to sleep with him.
虽然说两个兄弟变成基友
Not that there's anything wrong with
睡一起也没啥不好
two bros sleeping together.
我又没有兄弟恐惧症
I'm not bromophobic.
但我跟他就不是那种关系
It's just not what this is.
所以你确定你跟他之间
So you're sure there's nothing sexual
没有任何一点情欲元素吗
going on between you and him?
我确定
Yes, I'm sure.
瞎了眼了
No!
看好了 我要去雪泳
Watch, I'm gonna take a snow swim.
也没多冷嘛
Not that cold.
你说得对 完全没有任何情欲
You're right, nothing sexual there
除非你对穿着儿童内裤的大人有性趣
unless you like adult men in underoos.
要看到尼可拉斯了 我真心没心理准备
Well, there's Nicolas. I was not prepared for this.
是吗 老娘整趟来这里的地铁上
Really? 'cause we spent the entire subway ride
都在帮你做心理建设
preparing you for this.
你们两个会尴尬到
Okay, look, should I brace myself
我需要现在就做好准备吗
for weirdness between you two?
我是指现在就先开始喝吗
And by that, I mean should I hit this?
我会冷酷对待 酷到狂拽屌炸天
No, I'm cool. Cool as a cucumber.
冷酷冰雪女王 天下第一酷
Ll Cool J. Never been cooler.
我这口酒应该留到你说完这傻话再喝
Ugh! Why didn't I drink before you said that?
放心吧 我会对他冷眼相待
Oh, yeah. I am gonna ice him out.
你还是稍微收起你的冷酷范吧
Well, maybe lose a couple of those cubes,
毕竟他可是你老板
because he is your boss,
而我能念得起这学校全是靠
and the only reason I can afford to go here is
你在办公室的工作换来的
'cause you work in the office.
放心 他不会察觉
Don't worry, he'll never know.
假装你是尼可拉斯
Pretend you're Nicolas.
你好啊 卡洛琳
Hello, Caroline.
我是个貌美如花的美男子
I am a man, but I am pretty like a lady.
早安 今天好吗
Good morning, how are you?
好演技
Ooh, that was good.
麦克斯 早上好
'Sup, Max?
-你看我跟谁一起搭电梯上来了 -麦克斯
- Look who I got to ride up with. - Hey, Max.
嘿 朱迪 你听过人家这么叫吗
Hey, Jude. You ever heard that one before?
听过啊 这是啥流行语吗
Yeah. Is that, like, a thing?
迪克 谢谢你了
Thanks for the ride up, Deke.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
我本来以为得跟她搭货物运送电梯了
I thought we were gonna have to take the freight elevator.
是吗 我以为你们是要搭屁动扶梯呢
Really? I assumed you guys would take the ass-calator.
你好啊 卡洛琳
Oh, hello, Caroline.
早安 你好吗
Good morning, how are you?
很好 谢谢问候
Very well, thank you.
你看不出来我在生你气吗
Can't you see I'm mad at you?
那你为什么在笑
Then why are you smiling?
这是我假客套的脸
This is my fake face.
那你真的表情是怎么样呢
Then what does your real face look like?
你个已婚男人居然还敢亲我
How dare you kiss me when you're married?
我还是喜欢你假客套的脸
I prefer the fake one.
大家好吗
Bonjour, class.
尼可拉斯大厨好
Bonjour, chef Nicolas.
我们今天要特别多讲讲烘焙的化学知识
Today, we will be concentrating on the chemistry of baking
因为明天考试会考
for tomorrow's test.
我不知道考试结果会如何
I don't know about the damn test,
但如果考玩她屁股 我一定满分
but I would ace a pop quiz on that ass.
-真不好意思 -我去捡
- Oh, sorry. - I'll get that.
让朱迪捡啊
Let Judy pick it up.
好有机会看到她屁股晃动的样子
It's a chance to see it in motion.
你觉得她那屁股是从金·卡戴珊家买的吗
You think she got that thing at a Kim Kardashian backyard sale?
当你加水进面粉团中水合两种蛋白质
When you add water to the flour to hydrate the two proteins,
麦谷蛋白与醇溶蛋白
glutenin and gliadin,
这两种蛋白质会被对方吸引
those two proteins are drawn to each other,
从而融为一体
and they bond.
我喜欢称之 为对方欲罢不能
Like I like to say, they're hot for each other.
麦克斯你看 它们被对方吸引
Max, look, they were drawn to each other,
融为一体
they bonded,
现在生出了我们自己的大屁股了
and now, we've got our own big butt.
那屁股 真粉
Dat ass, though!
是那屁股 面粉吧
More like dat ass dough.
你们得往面团里加水
You need to wet the dough with water
才能保持湿润与柔软
to keep it moist and supple.
把面团弄湿 大家
Wet your bread, everyone,
把你们的面团弄湿
wet your bread.
我的挺湿了 你的呢
Mine's pretty wet. How's yours?
本来是 但吃抗忧郁药后 湿不起了
Mine would be, but it's on antidepressants.
跟你的搭档合作 帮助对方
Work with your partner, help each other out.
来 我帮你吧 麦克斯
Here, let me help, Max.
对啊 我的好像没你的光滑
Yeah, mine's not as smooth as yours.
继续揉吧 还需要更多水
Mm, keep kneading it. You need more water.
现在好多了吧
It's better, right?
对啊 把它弄湿挺管用的
Yeah, I think wetting it helped.
卡洛琳 我出大问题了
Caroline, something is really wrong with me.
先别慌 有我呢
Don't freak out. I'm here for you.
除非那是能传染给我的"问题"
Unless it's something I can catch.
出了件怪事
Something weird happened.
我可能对迪克有好感
I think I might have feelings for Deke.
天啊 不是吧
Oh, God, no!
我的意思是这事有意思 咱们来谈谈吧
I mean, that is interesting. Let's talk about that.
我不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do.
我把他当兄弟 我不想破坏我们之间的友情
We're bros, and I don't want to ruin the friendship,
这太不像我了
which is really unlike me.
我向来都是友情破坏王
I always ruin friendships.
打从你搬进来 我就一直想破坏我们的友情
I've been trying to ruin ours since you moved in.
迪克有何变化让你动了心
Well, what changed with Deke?
当时情景特别奇怪 他帮我加湿我的面团
It was so weird-- he was wetting my bread,
然后揉着揉着我"下面"包也湿了 你懂的
And then my bread was wet, if you know what I'm saying.
我懂 多谢你 我终于不爱吃面包了
Okay, thank you. I'm finally off bread.
我完全理解你
Look, I understand.
有时候人们就是会控制不住喜欢上谁
You can't always help who you're attracted to.
就像我和尼可拉斯
It's like with me and Nicolas--
我们才不像你和那个法国佬呢
This is not the same as you and Frenchie.
我是今天才开始对迪克有好感
I wasn't attracted to Deke before today.
而你第一次见尼可拉斯时
The first time you met Nicolas,
你的阴道都立马掉到地上 想爬上他大腿了
your vagina fell on the floor and tried to crawl up his leg.
没错 但我立刻捡起来并立马装了回去
Yes, but I scooped it up and snapped it back on
因为我天生就不是跟已婚男人乱搞的浪荡女
Because I was not born to have sex with a married man.
如果我是 我早就在马特·劳厄尔
If I was, I would have flirted with Matt Lauer
来我家参加圣诞树点亮仪式时 跟他调情了
when he came over for the Christmas tree lighting at my house.
马特·劳厄尔 那家伙可招妞喜欢了
Matt lauer-- that guy's got game.
虽然头发少 但妞多
No hair, but game.
各位 好消息
Hey, everybody, good news!
我的肾结石没了
Oh, I passed that kidney stone.
没错 我觉得是滑雪让它滑出来了
Yeah, I think the skiing loosened it.
感觉就像从我眼洞里生出了个小宝宝
Oh, I felt like I was birthing a baby through my eye hole.
你没有留着那些石头吗
Did you save the stone?
再三块 就能给我做条她那样的项链了
'cause only three more, and you can make me that necklace.
麦克斯 别试图转移话题
Max, don't change the subject.
迪克的事你打算怎么做
What are you gonna do about Deke?
慢着 我最喜欢给人建议了
Oh, wait, I love giving advice.
在波兰 我有自己的建议专栏
I had my own advice column in Poland.
名字就叫"千万别啊"
It was called "Don't do that!"
苏菲 你有跟朋友上过床吗
Sophie, have you ever had sex with a friend?
不是吧 你们俩要上床了吗
Oh, no. Are you two gonna do it?
当然不是 她的意思是
No, that is not what--
千万别啊
Oh, don't do that!
不要 这会破坏你们的友情
No, it will ruin your relationship
也会破坏我对麦克斯的印象
and my opinion of Max.
那你对我的印象就没影响吗
What about your opinion of me?
本来就已经很差了
Eh, it's already pretty low.
我跟迪克到底该怎么办
What am I gonna do about Deke?
他今晚还要过来学习
He's coming over to study tonight.
天啊 我好像50年代的怀春少女
Oh, God, I sound like such a girl from the '50s.
我要去抱着我的老式电话机哭了
Gonna go cry into my princess phone.
你应该告诉迪克你的真实感受
You should tell Deke how you feel,
今晚就告诉他
And tell him tonight,
因为我觉得那个朱迪也喜欢他
because I think that Judy girl likes him,
而且我觉得他也可能喜欢她
and I think he might like her too.
你为何这么说 虽说我完全不介意
Why do you say that? I literally don't care at all,
但我只想知道 你这话从何而来
but I just want to know, why would you say that?
麦克斯 他喜欢大屁股 他否认不了
Max, he likes big butts, and he cannot lie.
"糖会在什么温度下结晶
"At what temperature does sugar crystallize?
华氏度与摄氏度几度" 快答 麦克斯
fahrenheit and celsius." Go, Max.
麦克斯
Max.
你干嘛那样看着我
Why are you looking at me like that?
我完全无法理解
This doesn't make any sense!
那是因为你的书拿倒了
Well, your book is upside down.
我听到你们在叽叽喳喳的
Hey, hearing a lot of chitchat in here.
过来确认下你俩是否有在学习
Just wanted to make sure you two are studying.
学个屁啊 快亲他啊
Stop studying. Kiss him.
好啦 我还是走吧
All right, well, I better be going.
你们就当我不在好了
Just pretend I'm not here.
我向来如此
I always do.
有件事很奇怪 但在我们学习之前
Hey, um, this is weird, but before we study,
我有话要对你说
I kind of have something to tell you.
奇怪 我也有话要对你说
Weird, 'cause I kinda have something to tell you.
那真是太巧了 或许咱俩说的是同一件事
That is weird. Maybe it's the same thing.
有人想跟我做爱
Someone wants to have sex with me.
你怎么知道
How did you know that?
因为大屁股朱迪刚发短信给我
'cause Judy with the booty just texted me,
"你今晚想跟我一起学习
"Would you like to study tonight
然后顺便做个爱吗"
and then have sex with me?"
我觉得你对她意思解读的很到位
I think you've interpreted that correctly.
哇 她真直接 而且有够淫荡的
Wow, she's direct and, I might add, slutty.
我知道 她屁股大胆子也大
I know, she's got balls to go with that butt.
你刚想跟我说什么
So what were you gonna tell me?
我刚想说的话跟你刚告诉我的一样
Oh, I was going to tell you what you just told me,
大屁股朱迪想跟你做爱
That Judy with the booty wants to have sex with you.
很高兴她能鼓起勇气告诉你
Glad she got up the guts to tell you.
那你去上她吧
So go for it.
慢着 你想我去上了她吗
Wait, you want me to go for it?
对啊 没错 上她
Yeah, totally, go for it.
她看起来也不像有性病 上吧
She seems kind of clean. Go get it.
但我们说好了今晚要学习
But we're supposed to study.
我不想为了上她 而放你鸽子
I wouldn't want to bail on you just to go hit that.
如果你不去 那我去
Hey, if you don't, I will.
你真的不想上那对大屁股吗
You're really gonna pass that ass up?
快走吧 因为我得记住
Now get going, 'cause I have to memorize
在什么温度下糖糖糖会结成晶晶晶
what temperature cho-cho-cho turns into chan-chan-chan.
所以你是让我去吗
So you're telling me to go?
我就是说"走走走"吧
I'm saying, "Ta-ta-ta."
把她的"面包"搞湿 让它膨起来 兄弟
Go get her bread wet. Make it rise, bro.
好吧 兄弟
Okay, then, bro.
那我就去了 但那大屁股这么诱人
I guess I will go, but with that butt,
如果我回来后染上股沟瘾 那就全怪你
if I come back a crack addict, it's your fault.
他去哪里 是不是跑去买避孕套了
Where's he going? Is this a condom run?
他是跑去买避孕套了吗
Is he going on a condom run?
如果是的话 麻烦短信他顺便买健怡可乐
'cause if he is, can you text him to pick up a diet coke?
要罐装的 不要瓶装的 你懂的啦
Can, not a bottle. You know the deal.
他是去上朱迪
He's going to have sex with Judy.
你说得对 他也喜欢她
You were right, he's into her.
还好我没说什么
I'm so glad I didn't say anything.
会让我觉得很难过的话
that would have felt terrible.
那你现在感觉如何
How do you feel now?
很难过
Terrible.
但至少我没让自己丢脸
But at least I didn't embarrass myself.
我差点要给他看我的小矮人们了
I was this close to showing him my gnomes.
你一定很喜欢他
Wow, you must really like him
你都愿意让他知道
if you were willing to let him know
你是个神经病
that you're an insane person.
我很快就要比朱迪被操得更惨了
Well, I'm about to be more screwed than Judy,
因为我完全没学习
because I didn't study at all.
我懂法语 我可以帮你
I know French. I can help you.
你可以用尼可拉斯办公室的钥匙帮我
You can help me with the keys you have to Nicolas' office.
我们要潜进去偷试卷
We are breaking in and stealing the test!
你干嘛还要捂着他的耳朵 他知道你是惯犯
Why are you covering his ears? He knows you steal.
你就是从别人院子里把他偷走的
You took him from someone's yard.
真不敢相信我们为了偷你的试卷
I can't believe we're sneaking into his office
偷偷潜进他的办公室
to steal your test.
这完全是作弊行为
This is cheating.
别担心 我听说我的老师喜欢作弊[偷情]
Oh, don't worry, I hear my teacher's kind of into cheating.
一针见血
Can't argue with that.
麦克斯 麻利点 找到试卷
Max, please hurry. Find the test,
赶紧离开这里 因为我们不该来这里
and let's get out of here because we shouldn't be in here
这里都是他的味道 我好喜欢这味儿哦
and it smells like him and I like it.
好啦 其中一份肯定就是
Okay, one of these papers has to be it.
不是吧 这上面都是用密码写的
Oh, no, everything's written in secret code!
麦克斯 上面是法语
Max, that's French.
他人已经那么帅了 照片怎么能比
How is it possible he's even better-looking in photos
真人更好看呢
than in real life?
麦克斯 快点 我不能靠近他的东西
Max, hurry up. I can't be around his stuff.
我的阴道又试图想逃出我的裤子了
My vagina's trying to get out of my pants again.
那就把她放出来
Well, get her out here!
或许她可以帮我找到试卷
Maybe she can help me look for the test,
因为你一点用都没有
'cause you're useless.
天啊 是尼可拉斯
Oh, no, it's Nicolas.
我能闻到他在走廊里 我好爱
I can smell him in the hall, and I like it.
麦克斯 咱们快走吧
Max, let's get out of here.
好吧 你得留下来分散他的注意力
Okay, well, you have to stay and distract him,
这样我才能溜走
so I can sneak out.
你就假装你没生气 你是来找他的
Just pretend you're not mad and you came in to see him.
我不能瞬间转变态度啊
I can't just turn it on like that.
你以为我是鸡尾酒派对上的女演员啊
What am I, an actress at a cocktail party?
你非做不可 这是你出现在这里的
You have to, it's the only logical explanation
唯一合理解释
You have for being in here.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
我很想你 所以我就来你办公室了
I've missed you. I'm in your office.
这是我出现在这里的唯一合理解释
That's the only logical explanation I have for being in here.
抱歉 我弄疼你了吗
Oh, sorry. Did I hurt you?
不是 我坐在什么东西上了
Oh, no, I'm sitting on something.
不好意思 这是今天的试卷
Oh, sorry. Oh, those are the exams for today.
那我把这些试卷全扔地上
Oh, well, let me just give us some room
好腾出地方让我们亲热
while I push these exams on the floor.
继续吻我 不过这一次要整个人趴在我身上
Now, kiss me again, but this time, lay on top of me,
这样你的脚才不会碍事 快点
so your legs are out of the way. Now, go!
慢着 慢着 停下来
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
你知道这样是不对的 你已经结婚了
You know this can't happen. You're married.
不好意思
Now, if you'll excuse me,
现在我得去把某物装上了
I have to go snap something back on.
这是试卷的答案
Well, here are the test answers,
但我不知道问题是什么
but I don't know what the questions are
因为我只拿到一半试卷
because I only got half the test,
而且我只有一半确定那上面的是答案
and I'm only half sure those are the answers.
兄弟 你怎么搞到的
Whoa, dude, how did you get this?
我让卡洛琳出卖了灵肉
I turned Caroline into a whore.
你能看明白吗
Can you figure out any of this?
我完全猜不到这些问题会是什么
I don't have any idea what these questions could be.
我昨晚也没学习
Ugh! I didn't study either.
我和朱迪聊天 而且聊得很深入
Judy and I got to talking, and it got pretty involved.
现在我们都搞砸了
Well, now we're screwed.
我是说 反正你已经"搞"过了
I mean, you already got screwed.
恭喜 以你为傲 兄弟
Congrats. Proud of you, bro.
麦克斯 这次考试我们要不及格了
Max, we're gonna flunk this test.
我最好先去男厕所
Better go to the men's room
把所有答案抄上我鸡鸡了
and write all the answers on my penis.
别担心 能全写下
Don't worry, they'll fit.
这下你开心啦
I hope you're happy,
我跟已婚男人接吻了两次
I've now kissed a married man twice.
给 这是从尼可拉斯办公室拿来的
Oh, and here, I grabbed this from Nicolas' office.
那不是试卷 这是话费单
That's not the test. It's a phone bill.
我知道 我想你看他都没怎么跟老婆打电话
I know, I wanted you to see he doesn't call his wife much.
着火了 大家快出去
Fire! Everyone get out!
挪开你的大屁股 不然我们都要死在这里 滚
Move your big ass! We're gonna burn! Scoot.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max!
我希望尼可拉斯没事
I hope Nicolas is okay!
别担心我 我就在你身后
Don't worry about me, I'm right behind you!
卡洛琳 我要保证你安全 跟我走
Caroline, I want you to be safe. Come with me.
你都结婚了 我就留在这烧死算了
You're married. I'll just stay here and burn.
卡洛琳 别傻了
Caroline, don't be crazy.
这都是你的错
This is all your fault.
别担心我 我就在你身后
Don't worry about me, I'm right behind you!
麦克斯 别跑
Max, wait.
这只是假警报而已 是我拉响的
It's just a false alarm. I pulled it.
厉害
So classy.
不然你肯定考不过
You weren't gonna pass that test,
我需要你跟我一起上课
and I need you in that class with me.
你是为了我才这么做的吗
You did this for me?
当然也是为了我自己 我肯定也考不过
Yeah, and for me too, I wasn't gonna pass either.
但当你刚才谈到我和朱迪时
But, look, when you were talking about me and Judy just now,
你看起来怪怪的
you seemed kind of weird, and--
我只是昨天突然有一刻感觉奇怪
Oh, hey, I just had a weird moment yesterday
当你在帮我弄湿面团时
when you were getting my dough wet
我好像变得有点性奋
and I kinda got turned on,
有点觉得自己喜欢你 很恶心对吧
sort of thought I liked you. Yeah, gross, right?
对啊 超级恶心
Oh, right, yeah. Totally gross.
总而言之 我们是哥儿们
Anyway, dude, we're just bros.
好吧 哥们 但我要告诉你
Okay, bro, but just so you know,
昨晚我和朱迪什么事都没干
nothing happened between me and Judy last night.
太逊了吧 如果你喜欢一个女生
That's lame-- if you like a girl,
你应该紧紧抱住她 亲她
you should just grab her and kiss her.
好吧
Okay.
这会让你觉得奇怪吗
Was that weird?
会 不过我喜欢
Yeah. And I liked it.
麦克斯 快走
Max, come on!
抱歉打扰了
Sorry to interrupt,
但所有人都应该撤离这栋楼
but we're supposed to evacuate the building.
没着火啦 是迪克拉响的警报
There's no fire. Deke pulled the alarm.
我想亲她而已
I wanted to kiss her.
对啊 结果发现他喜欢基情
Yeah. Turns out he's into dudes.